http://www.centurydesign.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | CENTURY DESIGN, INC.
HomeAbout UsABOUT CDICDI VISIONCDI HISTORYProductsContact UsMoreHomeAbout UsABOUT CDICDI VISIONCDI HISTORYProductsContact Us(858) 292-1212(858) 292-1212HomeAbout UsProductsContact Us
Privacy Policy  This privacy policy informs CDI website users of the privacy practices for centurydesign.com. This privacy policy applies to information collected by this
website. You will be notified regarding:
What personally identifiable information is collected and how it is used.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information collected.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
CDI is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. CDI only has access to collect information that you voluntarily offer via website contact form, email, or direct contact from you. CDI will not sell or rent your information.CDI will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted CDI. CDI will not share your information with a third party, other than necessary to fill your request. Your Access to Control Information
You may opt out of future contact from CDI at any time by sending a request via email address or phone number listed on the CDI website. You have the right to:· See what information CDI has about you, if any.· Change and/or correct any data CDI has about you.· Express any concern you have about the use of your data.Security
CDI takes precautions to protect your personal information. When you submit information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Copyright © 2019 Century Design Inc. (CDI) - All Rights Reserved.Composites WorldPrivacy Policy
